Guide to the Bristol Family Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- LEGAL FILES, 1803-1872; Series V
  - Daggett and Bristol
    - Candee, L. and Co., 1872 (Box 11, Folder 257)
    - Central R.R. and Banking Co., 1852 (Box 11, Folder 258)
    - Dearborn, J.F., 1852 (Box 11, Folder 259)
    - Durant and Cattling, 1872-1873 (Box 11, Folder 260)
    - Dyer, John C. and Co., 1871-1872 (Box 11, Folder 261)
    - Gobde and Co., 1871-1872 (Box 11, Folder 262)
    - Gordon and Murray, 1871-1872 (Box 11, Folder 263)
    - Hall and Brother, 1871-1872 (Box 11, Folder 264)
    - Hempstead and Kitkpatrick, 1870-1872 (Box 12, Folder 265)
    - Henrie Brothers, 1872 (Box 12, Folder 266)
    - Hooper, Eldridge and Co., 1871-1872 (Box 12, Folder 267)
    - Kirby, R.N., 1872 (Box 12, Folder 268)
    - Mather, J.C., 1872 (Box 12, Folder 269)
    - Morris and Evans, 1871-1872 (Box 12, Folder 270)
    - N.P. Woods and Cutting, 1871-1872 (Box 12, Folder 271)
    - Omaha Smelting and Refining Co., 1871-1872 (Box 12, Folder 272)
    - Palmer, Henry, 1871 (Box 12, Folder 273)
    - Parkhurst, D.W., 1871 (Box 12, Folder 274)
    - Richmond, W.T. and Co., 1871-1872 (Box 12, Folder 275)
    - Robinson and Son, 1871-1872 (Box 12, Folder 276)
    - Roots, P.H, and F.M., 1871 (Box 12, Folder 277)
    - Salt Lake City National Bank, 1872 (Box 12, Folder 278)
    - Salt Lake Daily Tribune, 1871-1872 (Box 12, Folder 279)
    - Scott, Dunham and Co., 1871-1872 (Box 12, Folder 279)
    - Secretary's Office, Utah Territory, 1871 (Box 12, Folder 280)
    - Sisson, Wallace and Co., 1871-1872 (Box 12, Folder 281)
    - Sloan, W.S., 1872 (Box 12, Folder 282)
    - Snyder, G.G., 1871 (Box 12, Folder 283)
    - Stevenson, C.L., 1871 (Box 12, Folder 284)
    - Teasdel and. Co., 1871 (Box 12, Folder 285)
    - Union Iron Works, 1871 (Box 12, Folder 286)
    - Union Pacific Railroad, 1871-1872 (Box 12, Folder 287)
    - Utah and California Lumber Co., 1871-1872 (Box 12, Folder 288)
    - Utah Silver Mining Co. Ltd., 1871-1872 (Box 12, Folder 289)
    - Webster, D.P., 1871 (Box 12, Folder 290)
    - Wells, Fargo and Co., 1872 (Box 12, Folder 291)
    - White, A.W. and Co., 1871-1872 (Box 12, Folder 292)
    - Woods, N.P. and Co., 1871-1872 (Box 12, Folder 293)
  - Walker and Bristol
    - A - Z (Box 12, Folder 294-297)
    - Miscellanea, 1845-1846 (Box 12, Folder 298)
  - Miscellanea
    - A - Z (Box 13, Folder 299-306)
    - Adams, Rufus, 1817-1819 (Box 13, Folder 307)
    - Allen, John, 1805 (Box 13, Folder 308)
    - Barker, Anne, undated (Box 13, Folder 309)
    - Barker, George, 1809-1815 (Box 13, Folder 310)
    - Barker, Mary, 1812 (Box 13, Folder 311)
    - Barney, Hanover, 1803-1810 (Box 13, Folder 312)
    - Braisted, Elizabeth, 1851 (Box 13, Folder 313)
    - Braisted, Jacob, 1850 (Box 13, Folder 314)
    - Chetwood, MaryAnn, 1821 (Box 13, Folder 315)
    - Chetwood, William, 1827 (Box 13, Folder 316)
    - Smith, Nathan, 1805 (Box 13, Folder 317)
- MISCELLANEOUS PAPERS, 1767-1874; Series VI
  - 1767 - 1810 (Box 14, Folder 318-329)
  - 1811 - 1819 August 15 (Box 15, Folder 330-341)
  - 1819 August 15 - 1827 March (Box 16, Folder 342-354)
  - 1827 April - 1840 (Box 17, Folder 355-366)
  - 1841 - 1845 August (Box 18, Folder 367-377)
  - 1845 September - 1847 December (Box 19, Folder 378-390)
  - 1848 January - 1850 January (Box 20, Folder 391-402)
  - 1850 February - 1852 February (Box 21, Folder 403-414)
  - 1852 March - 1854 March (Box 22, Folder 415-426)
  - 1854 April - 1871 August 9 (Box 23, Folder 427-438)
  - 1871 August 10 - 1872 July 15 (Box 24, Folder 439-450)
  - 1872 July 16 - 1874 (Box 25, Folder 451-462)
  - undated (Box 26, Folder 463-474)
  - undated (Box 27, Folder 475-485)
  - undated (Box 28, Folder 486-497)
  - undated (Box 29, Folder 498-501)
- FAMILY PAPERS, 1789-1929; Series VII
  - Allen, Frederick, 1816 (Box 30, Folder 502)
  - Agnaw, Nellie, undated (Box 30, Folder 503)
  - Angier, Anna Louise, 1848 (Box 30, Folder 504)
  - Bliss, Emily C.
    - Bristol, Caroline, undated (Box 30, Folder 505)
    - Bristol, Mary Walcott, 1836-1844 (Box 30, Folder 506)
    - Murdoch, Frances Louise, 1807 (Box 30, Folder 507)
  - Bliss, Lucy, 1846 (Box 30, Folder 508)
  - Bliss, William
    - Bliss, Emily, 1866 (Box 30, Folder 509)
    - Murdoch, Frances Louisa, 1838 (Box 30, Folder 510)
  - Bristol, Albert G.
    - Bristol, Louis, 1822-1857 (Box 30, Folder 511)
    - Bristol, Sarah, 1830-1845 (Box 30, Folder 512)
    - Bristol, William, 1822-1833 (Box 30, Folder 513)
    - Bristol, William and Sarah, 1830 (Box 30, Folder 514)
    - Dwight, Timothy, 1827-1833 (Box 30, Folder 515)
    - Murdoch, Frances Louisa, 1830 (Box 30, Folder 516)
  - Bristol, Caroline
    - Bristol, John W., 1872-1874 (Box 30, Folder 517)
    - Bristol, Mary B., 1867-1886 (Box 30, Folder 518-519)
    - Bristol, Mary B. and Caroline L., 1876-1879 (Box 30, Folder 520)
    - Bristol, Sarah, 1858-1859 (Box 30, Folder 521)
    - Bristol, William B., 1864-1865 (Box 30, Folder 522)
    - Dana, Caroline Louise, 1868-1879 (Box 30, Folder 523)
    - Murdoch, Frances Louisa, 1865 (Box 30, Folder 524)
  - Bristol, Caroline Bliss, 1835-1847 (Box 30, Folder 525)
  - Bristol, Jeremiah G., 1820 (Box 30, Folder 526)
  - Bristol, John Walcott
    - Bliss, Emily C., undated (Box 30, Folder 527)
    - Bristol, Caroline, 1870 (Box 30, Folder 528)
    - Bristol, Mary B., 1869-1874 (Box 30, Folder 529)
    - Miscellanea, undated (Box 30, Folder 530)
  - Bristol, John and Mary Walcott, 1859 (Box 30, Folder 531)
  - Bristol, Lewis K., certificate of appreciation from Union Trust Company on the occasion of his death, 1910 July 21 (Box 44)
  - Bristol, Louis Henry
    - Bristol, Caroline B., undated (Box 30, Folder 532)
    - Bristol, Louis, 1856-1857 (Box 30, Folder 533)
    - Bristol, Mary Walcott, undated (Box 30, Folder 534)
    - Bristol, William B., 1863-1864 (Box 30, Folder 535)
  - Bristol, Louis and Mary, 1853 (Box 30, Folder 536)
  - Bristol, Mary Bliss
    - Bliss, William, undated (Box 30, Folder 537)
    - Bristol, Caroline, 1870 (Box 30, Folder 538)
    - Dana, Caroline Louise, 1879 (Box 30, Folder 539)
    - Bristol, John W., 1870-1874 (Box 30, Folder 540)
  - Bristol, Mary Walcott
    - Bristol, Louis, 1844-1859 (Box 30, Folder 541)
    - Cleaveland, Mary Sanford, 1845 (Box 30, Folder 542)
  - Bristol, Mary Walcott
    - Bliss, Emily C., 1835-1838 (Box 30, Folder 543)
    - Bliss, Lucy, 1835-1842 (Box 31, Folder 544)
    - Bliss, Moses, 1841 (Box 31, Folder 545)
    - Bliss, William, 1836-1837 (Box 31, Folder 546)
    - Bliss family, 1846 (Box 31, Folder 547)
    - Bristol, Caroline, 1848 (Box 31, Folder 548)
    - Bristol, Louis, 1840 (Box 31, Folder 549)
    - Bristol, Louis Henry, 1847 (Box 31, Folder 550)
    - Bristol, Sarah, 1836-1848 (Box 31, Folder 551)
    - Sykes, M., undated (Box 31, Folder 552)
  - Bristol, Sarah
    - Bristol, Louis, 1826-1858 (Box 31, Folder 553)
    - Bristol, Mary D., 1845 (Box 31, Folder 554)
    - Bristol, William, 1850 (Box 31, Folder 555)
    - Bristol, William Brooks, 1820 (Box 31, Folder 556)
    - Jones, Eliza P.F., 1856 (Box 31, Folder 557)
    - Murdoch, Frances Louisa, 1866 (Box 31, Folder 558)
  - Bristol, Simeon
    - Bristol, Abigail B., 1816-1817 (Box 31, Folder 559)
    - Bristol, William, 1822-1826 (Box 31, Folder 560)
    - Champeon, Epaphrodites, 1798-1799 (Box 31, Folder 561)
  - Bristol, Theodore, 1929 (Box 31, Folder 562)
  - Butler, M., 1861 (Box 31, Folder 563)
  - Catlin, Abijah, 1827 (Box 31, Folder 564)
  - Champeon, Epaphrodites, 1798-1799 (Box 31, Folder 565)
  - Chaplain, Ann Francis
    - Bristol, Mary B., 1876 (Box 31, Folder 566)
    - Bristol, Sarah, undated (Box 31, Folder 567)
    - Murdoch, Frances Louisa, 1834-1842 (Box 31, Folder 568)
  - Child, Laura, 1845 (Box 31, Folder 569)
  - Cleaveland, Mary Sanford
    - Bristol, Louis, 1844-1854 (Box 31, Folder 570-571)
    - Bristol, Mary Dwight, 1847-1854 (Box 31, Folder 572)
    - Cleaveland, William, 1853-1854 (Box 31, Folder 573)
    - Cleaveland, William and Mary Dwight, 1847-1853 (Box 31, Folder 574)
    - Miscellanea (Box 31, Folder 575)
  - Cleaveland, William Pitt
    - Bristol, Louis, 1847-1857 (Box 31, Folder 576)
    - Bristol, Mary Dwight, 1844 (Box 31, Folder 577)
    - Miscellanea (Box 31, Folder 578)
    - Coit, Francis A., 1844 (Box 31, Folder 579)
    - Cornelius, M., 1857 (Box 31, Folder 580)
    - Daggett, Ellsworth, 1871 (Box 31, Folder 581)
  - Dana, Caroline Louise
    - Bristol, Caroline, 1870 (Box 32, Folder 582)
    - Bristol, Eugene Stuart, 1873 (Box 32, Folder 583)
    - Bristol, John Walcott, 1872 (Box 32, Folder 584)
    - Bristol, Mary Bliss, 1866-1879 (Box 32, Folder 585-588)
    - Bristol, William Brooks, 1870 (Box 32, Folder 589)
  - Dent, Henry Hatch, 1843 (Box 32, Folder 590)
  - Draper, Minnie L., 1879 (Box 32, Folder 591)
  - Edwards, Henrietta, 1849-1850 (Box 32, Folder 592)
  - Edwards, Ogden
    - Bristol, Sarah, 1849 (Box 32, Folder 593)
    - Bristol, William, 1808-1814 (Box 32, Folder 594)
  - Edwards, Pierrepont, 1814 (Box 32, Folder 595)
  - Evans, Anna C., undated (Box 32, Folder 596)
  - Fisher, George Park, 1876-1880 (Box 32, Folder 597)
  - Flagg, Hezebiah, 1804 (Box 32, Folder 598)
  - Frazer, George, 1797 (Box 32, Folder 599)
  - Harris, Jedidiah, 1814 (Box 32, Folder 600)
  - How, Zaidee Kent, 1879 (Box 32, Folder 601)
  - Heermann, E., 1836 (Box 32, Folder 602)
  - Hosmer, Stephen Titus, 1827 (Box 32, Folder 603)
  - Howland, Josey, 1836 (Box 32, Folder 604)
  - [Folder numbers not used] (Box 32, Folder 605-609)
  - Hunt, Lulu B., 1879 (Box 32, Folder 610)
  - Jones, Eliza Perkins, 1864 (Box 32, Folder 611)
  - Jones, Marie R., 1860 (Box 32, Folder 612)
  - Klauser, Lina, 1879 (Box 32, Folder 613)
  - Kinsburg, A., 1798 (Box 32, Folder 614)
  - Lewis, Sarah H., 1857 (Box 32, Folder 615)
  - Linsley, Jared, 1832 (Box 32, Folder 616)
  - McKim, Lattie F., 1840 (Box 32, Folder 617)
  - Mansfield, Emily D., 1865 (Box 32, Folder 618)
  - Mansfield, Mary, 1879 (Box 32, Folder 619)
  - Murdoch, Esther, 1841, undated (Box 32, Folder 620)
  - Murdoch, Frances Louisa
    - Bristol, Louis, 1844-1866 (Box 32, Folder 621)
    - Bristol, Mary Wolcott, 1838 (Box 32, Folder 622)
    - Bristol, Sarah, 1854-1866 (Box 32, Folder 623)
  - Murdoch, Jane, 1838-1842 (Box 32, Folder 624)
  - Murdoch, John, 1835 (Box 32, Folder 625)
  - Murdoch, William B., 1863 (Box 32, Folder 626)
  - Nicoll, Alice S., 1880 (Box 32, Folder 627)
  - Ogden, D., 1799 (Box 32, Folder 628)
  - Paine, Sarah M.
    - Bristol, Louis, 1856-1857 (Box 33, Folder 629)
    - Bristol, Sarah, 1856 (Box 33, Folder 630)
  - Parke, Melanie, 1879 (Box 33, Folder 631)
  - Pendleton, Nathaniel, 1806 (Box 33, Folder 632)
  - Perkins, Annie W., undated (Box 33, Folder 633)
  - Porter, Fidelia, 1836 (Box 33, Folder 634)
  - Porter, Sarah D., 1864 (Box 33, Folder 635)
  - Porter, Theodore W., 1849 (Box 33, Folder 636)
  - Porter, Timothy Dwight, 1855 (Box 33, Folder 637)
  - Price William, 1809 (Box 33, Folder 638)
  - Seely, Ebenezer, 1848 (Box 33, Folder 639)
  - Sheddin, Jean, 1853 (Box 33, Folder 640)
  - Skinner, Aaron, 1844-1845 (Box 33, Folder 641)
  - Skinner, Aaron, 1845 (Box 33, Folder 642)
  - Skinner, C.S., 1836 (Box 33, Folder 643)
  - Staples, John B., 1821 (Box 33, Folder 644)
  - Stibbins, Antoinette, 1879 (Box 33, Folder 645)
  - Stoddard, Maria Teresa, 1852-1853 (Box 33, Folder 646)
  - Stratton, Joseph, 1848 (Box 33, Folder 647)
  - Strong, Emily S., 1879 (Box 33, Folder 648)
  - Taft, John Adams, 1826 (Box 33, Folder 649)
  - Tappan, Sarah L., 1836-1839 (Box 33, Folder 650)
  - Thomson, James, 1808 (Box 33, Folder 651)
  - Trask, Eliza L., 1831-1835 (Box 33, Folder 652)
  - Van Santvoard, Katherine, 1879 (Box 33, Folder 653)
  - Van Santvoard, Zaidee, 1879 (Box 33, Folder 654)
  - Van Wyck, William, 1823-1828 (Box 33, Folder 655)
  - Whitney, Elizabeth, 1838-1839 (Box 33, Folder 656)
  - Whitney, Henrietta Frances, 1836 (Box 33, Folder 657)
  - Wolcott, A., undated (Box 33, Folder 658)
  - Unidentified, undated (Box 33, Folder 659)
- PERSONAL PAPERS, 1774-1865; Series VIII
  - Bristol, Mary B.
    - Scrapbook, 1873-1874, 1877 (Box 34, Folder 660)
  - Bristol, Sarah
    - Account book, 1844 (Box 34, Folder 661)
  - Bristol, Simeon
    - Agreement, 1792 (Box 34, Folder 662)
    - Complaint, 1774 (Box 34, Folder 663)
  - Cleaveland, Mary Sanford
    - Account book, 1842-1852 (Box 34, Folder 664)
    - Grocery accounts, 1852-1854 (Box 34, Folder 665)
  - Heerman, Lewis
    - Account book, 1805-1813 (Box 34, Folder 666)
    - Bank books, 1812-1819 (Box 34, Folder 667-668)
  - Lum, Henry
    - Carpenter's accounts, 1849 (Box 34, Folder 669)
  - Mercer, William
    - Bank book, 1846 (Box 34, Folder 670)
  - Murdoch, Frances Louise
    - Essays and articles, undated (Box 34, Folder 671)
  - Stuart, E.C.
    - Account book, 1865 (Box 34, Folder 672)
  - Miscellanea
    - Account book, undated (Box 35, Folder 673)
    - Architectural estimates, undated (Box 35, Folder 674)
    - Articles, n. d. (Box 35, Folder 675)
    - Chemical Analyses record book, undated (Box 35, Folder 676)
    - Dry Goods Store account book, 1846 (Box 35, Folder 677)
    - Deeds, 1798-1854 (Box 35, Folder 678-681)
    - Demosthenes Oration on the Crown, undated (Box 35, Folder 682)
    - Genealogy, undated (Box 35, Folder 683)
    - Lecture notes, undated (Box 36, Folder 684-693)
    - Maps, 1856-1857 (Box 36, Folder 694)
    - Newspaper clippings, undated (Box 36, Folder 695)
    - Newspaper clippings, undated (Box 37, Folder 696)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 37, Folder 697)
    - Play, 1830 (Box 37, Folder 698)
    - Poetry, 1830-1849 (Box 37, Folder 699)
    - Printed material, 1825-1873, undated (Box 37, Folder 700-705)
    - Shipping documents (in French), 1804 (Box 37, Folder 706)
    - Specifications, undated (Box 37, Folder 707)
- FINANCIAL RECORDS, Series IX
  - Bills, receipts, and cancelled checks (Box 38)
  - Bills, receipts, and cancelled checks (Box 39)
  - Bills, receipts, and cancelled checks (Box 40)
  - Bills, receipts, and cancelled checks (Box 41)
  - OVERSIZE
    - Bristol, Louis. Account Book, 1847-1853 (Box 42, Folder 708)
    - Cleaveland, William Pitt. Legal Accounts, 1838-1841 (Box 42, Folder 709)